

FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

mazejul@gmail.com +33(0)6.49.82.90.89 www.julien-maze.com After 4 years of experience in web development, looking to move to Glasgow, Scotland. Highly motivated, hard-working and attentive to details. Passion for solving challenging problems. Love new technologies and learning new things.

Experience

2012-2014

Front-End Web Developer

Dickson-Constant, Lille, France

- Translating static designs to a mobile and desktop interactive UI.
- Maintaining and evolving the existing websites.
- Improvements to a PHP REST API.
- UI improvements to an Actionscript 3 awning simulator (Dickson designer).
- Setting up project management tools (SVN, Redmine).
- Setting up and managing dedicated servers (Debian).

2011-2012

Web developer

Abase, Brest, France

- Front and back-end of an intranet website using Drupal.
- Improvements on a bank budgetting application (Java).
- Improvements on a bank CRM (Java).

2009-2010

Web developer ("sandwich course")

STDI, Lassay-les-Châteaux France

- Interactive school books for major French publishers.
- Educational apps using Actionscript 3.
- Actionscript 2 & 3

Education

2009-2010

Licence (one-year) in Multimedia and Web development

University Institute of Technology, Laval, France

• Web development, project management, e-learning, graphic design

2007-2009

University Diploma of Technology (two-years) in Communication Services and Networks

University Institute of Technology, Laval, France

 Web development, project management, graphic design, Front-End integration, photography, communication theory, networks administration

2007

Baccalauréat (French secondary school diploma), science major

Iroise High School, Brest, France

Skills

- HTML/CSS
- Javascript / jQuery
- · PHP / MySQL
- Drupal / Wordpress
- Responsive Web Design
- Cross Browser compatibility
- Java / GWT

- OS: Windows, Linux, Mac OS
- Tools: Sublime / Netbeans, Git / SVN, Photoshop, Illustrator, Jira, Redmine
- Currently learning: Node.js, AngularJS, LESS